Amy Lazo

AmyLazo.Work@gmail.com

An energetic University of Texas at Arlington student concurrently studying Finance and Accounting, seeking to implement resourceful analytical ideas for business. With 2 years of previous cliental service, strengthening communicative and software skills are also imperative ambitions.

EDUCATION

University of Texas at Arlington

Bachelor's in Finance and Accounting, Expected Graduation: May 2022

- · Overall GPA: 3.95 Major GPA: 4.00
- · Relevant Coursework:
 - · Financial & Managerial Accounting
 - · Investment & Business Finance
 - · Business Law

· Organizational Management

Accounting Information Systems

· Business Statistics

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

RaceTrac Petroleum, Arlington, TX

June 2018 – August 2020

Sales Associate

- Used handheld software to record inventory, credit damaged items, and transfer products to neighboring RaceTrac stores
- · Communicated with guests and thoroughly analyzed criticisms in order to maximize client satisfaction
- · Supervised shift teams to preform daily tasks and goals
- · Provided job training for various new associates simultaneously

TD Ameritrade, Southlake, TX

September 2020 – April 2021

Will complete two semesters as an Investor Services Intern, and contribute by:

- Being a member of a high-caliber team for a group case project throughout the year
- Participating in roundtable interactions with business partners and administrators
- Shadowing other TD Ameritrade departments such as equity and options trading, sales, brokerage clearing, and client service
- · Assisting TD Ameritrade clients via phone, and in other real-world situations

ACTIVITIES & PROJECTS

The Dental Sealant Program

March 2018

SkillsUSA Competitor

· Recognized at state level on The Dental Sealant Program, a project aimed to provide essential free dental care to children in low income families

The Accounting Society

August 2019 – June 2020

Member

A professional student organization providing insightful seminars of figures in the Accounting field

Management Group Case Project

January 2020 – April 2020

Student Collaborator

- · Cooperated amongst classmates in conducting an ethical solution for a hypothetical job conflict
- · Learned how to assess conflicts as an administrator, while also heightening presentational skills

SKILLS & INTERESTS

· Fluent in Spanish

Microsoft Word, PowerPoint, & Excel

· Time Management

· Financial Trends & Variances

· Critical Thinking

Financial Statements & Ratios